Guide to the Sylvester Nemes Papers1973-2010
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Photographs, Slides, and Memorabilia, 6; Series 6
  - Flies (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Legend of the Headwaters plaque, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Framed photograph of Soft Hackles, a Japanese fishing club, along with flies, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Slide binders
  - Spinners, 1990-1995 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Spinners, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Spinners, 1991-1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Spinners, 1987-1999 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Two Centuries, 1998-2000 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Scotland, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Scotland, 1990-1998; undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - [Various], 1984-1995 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - [Various], 1987-1996 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - [Various], 1982-1998 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - [Various], 1989-1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - [Various], 1982-2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - [Various], 1986-1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Mixed, 1987-2000 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - [Various], 1976-2005 (Box 35, Folder 8)